trootrac.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy Policy: TrooTrac

We are committed to protecting your personal data you provide to us. We take your privacy very seriously and assure you that we will process your data in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable laws. It is important to us that you can use and enjoy the website without having to compromise your privacy in any way.

The purpose of this policy is to clarify how will your personal data be used and processed.

**What information do we collect?**  
You will be required to provide us with the information on our website mentioned below while registering with us as an affiliate. 

|  | Name   
---|---  
| Telephone  
| Email-ID  
| Fax  
| Address  
| Website related information  
The information provided here will be used to send you the information requested by you. It will also enable us to improve our marketing, for purposes of administering our business activities, making available other products and services to our clients and potential clients. We may share non personal data such as website traffic details with our clients or partners. We will not share or sell any information about individual user.

You consent to the collection and use of personal information relating to you as set out in this privacy policy submitting your information and by using our website. Any changes or amendments to our privacy policies shall be posted on this page so that are aware of it. Please check back regularly. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes.

**Safeguarding Personal Data:**  
We use industry standard safeguards to protect the privacy of your personal data such as encryption keys, passwords, and firewalls. Your personal information will be held securely in India in accordance with the Data Protection Act, in addition to the company’s safeguards.

**Tracking Technology Privacy Policy:**  
**User:** A person or persons using a web browser to view a website.

**Use of Cookie:**  
Cookie is small piece of text file which is stored on user’s hard drive. Cookie can remember what information a user accesses on one web page to simplify subsequent transactions or to short cut access to the site. The technology uses cookies to track clicks, sales and leads and for member log in sessions. On certain sites or third party sites we may utilize cookies for other purposes such as order tracking in online shops or for targeting advertisements to particular types of visitor.

**Use of Web Beacons:**  
Our tracking technology utilizes a small piece of code commonly called a “Web Beacon” also referred to as “tracking pixel” or “action tag”. This tracking pixel will reside on merchant’s web page and will not be visible to the end user. Merchants program this tracking pixel via Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) in order to collect certain information about the user’s visit on their website. 

**Use of information:**  
The information stored with the use of cookies and web beacons can rarely contain Personally Identifiable Information (PII) about the user. Data that is stored in the databases includes only non-PII information which may incorporate Cookie ID, Affiliate ID, Advertiser ID, time of action, referral page, time of sale, product code, user’s IP (for auditing purpose), banner ID etc. This information is returned to us for processing and is used to remunerate the Affiliate for the referral, typically when a sale is made.

The data stored will not be sold, licensed or in any way transferred to another party apart from auditing purposes. We do not store or record any other information about the user, beyond what has been described above, and we do not use that information to expect or prepare for a User’s future action.
